[Music]
just landed in Brooklyn went to the H for some
just landed in Brooklyn like like damn I'm on my
villag came through it that fire he came with a literal stick
black T taking Hennessy sips with a rake in my grip in
place of a PL yo yo yo Sor I heard a hood need to rush out of sex
say less cuz I just landed in damn just landed in
Brooklyn went to the hood for some B sh say she from Bush wi
but she on P now give it top like she hopping on fill
dick she swallow my kids out the w Wait I just sled in the hood
F to smoke me a fresh pack of Ops wait fresh at up and
I'm stra I'm lit out the oong and liquor who want know
who want to SM to get pet up get turn over frame on a picture
my my bro got a stick in a straw hat came from a village
and scamers and killers from the struggle
and I could bet I'm the only team that could say this
for the homies out broke bread we split 50 when we were still on EBT
I'm trying to move the whole gang out the hood
tell the family go whole team going to eat ain't about blood about money
this family ties if I'm kid to day baby king pray for the day
when a br's going to eat till the the M was by any means
look I'm with the gang and we clicked up we might be deep
y'all look like some Shook Ones like rest of y'all suck my dick
like how see taste with it your whole lung up like I do this
so my brothers don't got to be busting the ass for no come up
like what I'm the one I leave them tick like they got to stut away
just landed in Brooklyn huh went to the H with some
say she from buwi but she giv it top like she hopping on filler dick
she swallow my kids off the W way I just landed in the hood
F to smoke me a fresh pack of Ops he going to be like this
Not Really Cooking ain't nobody ate that